Japanese Black Tea Sisters 100 Questions
I'm going to challenge you now.
I'll do my best.
Oh!
I'm Nanako Nishino.
I'm Anna Ishii.
I'm told I'm nothing special.
Me too
Lies.
That's great.
Oh, my God.
May 25, 1994. That's great.
May 25, '94.
July 11, 1998.
I'm probably about 158.
162.
I'm a king.
I'm Wang.
We're the same.
Osaka. It's Tokyo. It's sunny. I am right-handed. Also right-handed.
Well, I think it's a hassle.
I am a pain in the ass.
I think I am a pain in the ass in the eyes of others.
I think I am rough.
I think you are a pain in the ass.
Really?
I think I'm rough.
I think I'm probably
Q. What is your favorite alcoholic beverage?
It's good.
I like it.
It has a great aroma.
It is very delicious!
Q.Which sake makes you feel pampered the most?
It's a sake that spoils me with all its goodness.
The one who spoils you with all his/her strength.
I don't think I'm a spoiled person.
I prefer to be spoiled.
I want to be spoiled.
Q. Who is your favorite character?
Q. What was your favorite day?
Hmmm...
But I don't know.
I think I did my best.
I don't know...
I, um...
I've been using the bathtub for so long.
It's a bit of a hassle to shampoo from here.
I understand.
Sometimes I pamper her as I feel like it.
Q. What is your favorite android?
Q. How did you feel when you overflowed miso soup?
I see, I was surprised when I spilled some miso soup.
I'm surprised.
You did that?
I was surprised.
I'm trying to get my sister certified in neurology.
She's working hard on her neuro.
She's getting better at it.
Did you have it done?
Yeah, she did.
That's nice. Yeah.
It's hard.
No, but...
Yeah, it is.
I don't know.
I'll make it a bug.
I'm not very good at it.
I'm kind of a deep sea kind of guy.
Yeah, I'm not good at it either.
I'm not good at it. I'm not good at it either.
Q. Who is your favorite person in the sea?
Someone who is strong.
I like people who laugh a lot.
Q. Who is your favorite person in the sea?
I don't know.
I want to have a good time.
I wish I had a job.
Oh, I know.
I wish I was on the job too.I wish I could spend my time at work too.
Q.Is there anything your father doesn't have much of?
Not much.
You mean you don't have much for your father?
To your father.
Oh, I see.
Like his personality.
Personality.
Oh.
I don't get it.
I'm often told I have a similar cheerful personality.
You're kind.
That's amazing.
Like a friend.
He does a lot of work around the house.
I don't know.
But is it the amount of love?
Taro.
Oh, really?
I can't eat it.
I try once every few years.
But every time I'm like, "Not yet?
You're always asking me if I'm ready.
I don't know.
I'm afraid of the deep sea.
I'm afraid of the outdoors.
I'm a little scared to go there.
So cute!
What kind of food do you like?
I don't go to the beach.
Sure, I do.
Corn.
I love corn.
It's delicious.
What's your favorite place in the ocean?
Uh, I don't know.
Camping.
I know.
I want to go back.
Camping
I want to go in the ocean or something
Outdoors.
Which do you prefer?
Which one?
Do you think I'm a little twitchy? I don't know.
I don't know.
I guess I'd say she's a twat.
Really? Then let's say tsun.
I think I'm more of a twang myself.
It's hard to say.
Squid.
I'm a squid.
I can't eat hormone candy.
What I can't eat is hormone candy
What I can't eat is some hormone type
Yes
I am moss cheese
Ehh...
I don't like the hardened kind.
I sing
Eh, I see.
I play with dogs
Yup.
Short cut
Short cut.
It looks good on you.
Really?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I've never done it before in my life.
Yeah.
A little bit.
I want to do it.
I'd like to have a full head of blonde hair.
Oh, no?
No.
No?
You've always been dark, so it'd look good on you. No? No?
I've always been dark.It's always been black.
It's gonna look so good on you.
Oh, my God.
I want to do it.
Someday.
It's so extravagant.
I'd like to make a nice breakfast, like a little frozen yellowtail on rice.
Make a nice breakfast like yellowtail chazuke.
I don't know if it's extravagant
I don't know if it's extravagant, but I ate it.
It was delicious.
It's so cute.
I don't usually do that, so it was delicious.
It's true, the yellowtail chazuke was delicious.
I bought massage coupons.
That's nice.
It's a luxury, isn't it?
Art.
Japanese.
Math.
Science.
Dancing eh, where's science?
Hokkaido.
Okinawa.
Okinawa?
That's amazing.
You like a lot of things.
Mango Shine Muscat.
Q. What's a mango Shine Muscat?
Ehh...
Daikon radish
Egg
Q.What is the mango's Shine Muscat?
I don't know.
I think it was soggy
That's a lie, that's an absolute lie!
Well... umm...
I wanted to be a nurse.
I was studying. Me too.
Really?
Hey, wow! Actually...
Common
I actually studied nursing in high school.
Oh, yeah.
But I guess I wasn't used to it.
It was hard.
I couldn't keep up.
I had to do math... math.
Math.
It wasn't great.
Uh-oh.
I see.
Home.
Oh, no, home.
Home
home
Autumn
Eh, woman
Smile, I guess.
Smile Smile Smile Smile Smile Smile Smile Autumn I like women better
Smile... I knew it.
She's cute.
I like to drink my drinks warm like this.
You can see it in winter.
I think it's cute when I see it on a wall or something.
It depends on the time.
It depends on how long you have, like, two hours, maybe a half hour.
Not even an hour.
Half an hour.
I'll do 30 minutes.
It depends on the person.
Or the person you're going with.
Well, it depends on the time.
If you're really, really good together...
I can do it for hours.
I can wait an hour, but it depends on the person I'm going with, and the people I'm going with.I'm an hour away, and it depends on the person I'm with, and who I'm with, and, well, that's definitely a big factor, and it's just something that's amazing.
I can stand in line for hours.
What do you do because of your mom?
You know...
Uh, gargle, I guess.
Uh, gargle.
And feed him.
Oh, I see.
Grandma.
What do you do because of your mother?
What do you dream about, Mai?
I look at my cell phone.
I'll set the alarm.
What's your latest dream? What's your dream these days?
I don't know.
Did you have a dream that you were on vacation?
I had a dream... I don't remember where.
I dreamed I was traveling in Japan.
Oh, that sounds fun.
Sounds fun.
I dreamed that I was going to visit my grandmother with my family.
I wanted to take the last train home.
My brother drove me to the train station.
Oh, like that?
Harassing.
Yes, I was very nervous.
It was kind of a scary dream.
Oh, I see.
I woke up just in time, I don't know if I made it or not.
I was so nervous.
Q. What are your goals for the future?
Uh...
Hmmm...
I want to see the latest technology.
Oh, I see.
If I could go to the future.
But I'd like to see what I'd look like... if I could see myself.
You want to see yourself?
Yeah, I do.
I'd like to.
The past...
I don't think I'm gonna do anything.
What?
What, you don't think that's gonna change anything?
I've seen a lot of things in the past.
Just a tour?
Visiting.
But I'm on a family vacation.
I took an old family vacation.
Sounds fun.
I'd like to take a tour.
I've seen the movie. I'm impressed.
I could do that.
I'm in a play.
I only cry when I'm on set.
I don't cry.
That's how I cry.
I don't cry at my own private events.
I don't cry at private events.
Sometimes I cry when I'm moved, but that's just for dramatic effect.
I laugh a lot.
I watch some videos and it's funny.
I also watch videos of comedians, and I have a good reaction.
Chocolate
Q. I want to be able to understand the feelings of animals.
I also want to talk to my dog.
Q.How much do you weigh?
About 23.5cm
The same.
The same?
That's great.
How long are your mother's teeth?
Tough.
Teeth or teeth?
Teeth?
My front teeth are a little bigger.
I inherited them from my mother.
I have a scaffold? It's called a scaffold.
It's a little bit nasal.
You do?Is that so?
Yeah.
It's expensive.
Are you with your mother?
Yes, my mom and my brother are all together.
They're all the same.
But I guess I have a more optimistic outlook on things.
I'm focused.
On the other hand, I'm not so good at concentrating.
Oh, I see.
I'm already a pain in the ass.
Weaknesses
Solving riddles. Riddle, riddle, riddle...
Sauna
Trampline
Is trampoline a sport?
A sport on the edge.
I want to play Tramplin
I want to play soccer
I want to wear clothes in the corner of my smile
Oh, but I don't.
No? You weren't, were you? Yeah, I don't know... I don't know...
Yeah, something like that.
She called me Nanashi.
Heh.
I've always been An-chan
An-chan
I don't know...
The one I drew in kindergarten or something.
I think it's a cake shop.
Oh, it's so cute!
I think it's a classic.
That's a good one.
I was a nurse, and I'm pretty sure I drew a cake shop.
I was a nurse.
I played piano for a long time.
I worked really hard on my soroban.
Oh, my God.
Like 888 in the head.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great.
I took a lot of tests.
Yeah.
I don't know.
My parents used to wash me in the bathtub.
And then they put me on that towel.
What do you call it?
Pass? Pass?
When your parents do that pass thing.
Oh, that's when you were so tiny.
I don't know how much.
I don't know how much, but when I came out of this hot, humid bathroom.
I remember the cool breeze when I came out of this hot, humid bathroom.
I remember the feeling of being in a different mood.
That's funny.
I was about five years old.
I was about five years old when my little brother was born.
I'll never forget that feeling of...
I'll never forget how nervous we were.
I think that was the youngest I've ever been.
What's your favorite snack?
Udon noodles! Sweet potatoes!
Favorite color?
Well, I like both, but I'm a cat person.
I'm a dog person.
Blue. Blue.
Black.
Socializing.
Where?
I'm studying socializing.
That's deep.
Deep.
I'm studying.
I'm not really studying that much, but...
I'm not really studying it, but I'm learning about the birthplace of chocolate.
where it came from...I was learning a little bit the other day about stores, where they come from, and so on.
I was learning a little bit the other day.
How's winter?
It's good.
I think it's good too.
Winter, winter...
I don't know...
I might think about it every day.
Every day when I'm taking a bath.
It's a good day.
I tend to think, "I'm so happy.
When I go home to my parents, I tend to think, "That was a good day." I tend to think, "I'm happy.
That's nice.
When I go home to my parents.
When I get together with my family.
I'm happy.
When I go home, even if I don't do anything.
Oh, yeah, I'm going to bed.
They do everything for me.
I'm happy.
Plum, salmon
Plum, salmon.
When I'm off, it's about 8:00 a.m. Oh, that's early!
On my days off, I get up at 9:30 or so.
I'm in the dark by midnight.
That's right.
I also like to get into bed around 11:00 a.m. and go to sleep.
Is it a habit or a habit?
I look up everything.
It's a good habit.
I can ask about any word I hear, like, "What is that? I have a good habit of looking up words I hear, like, "What is that?
I'm always asking, "What's that? I'm always asking, "What is it?
Good habit
I touch my nose like this.
Sometimes.
That sounds like a lot.
You know, it's possible, isn't it?
You just don't know it.
I'm sure there are a lot of them.
I go out with my friends to solve mysteries.
I go to the movies, go for walks, etc,
I have a lot of plans.
- Wow. - I see.
I want to be busy, busy, busy.
Q. What makes you want to recognize what you are doing?
My cell phone.
What? I thought you said it was disconnected.
Is that okay?
I don't know. I don't know.
Records.
Uh, photos...
Notes.
Photographs.
I mean...
I don't know if I can live with that.
I don't know if I'll be able to live, but I'll keep a record of it all.
I don't think I can cook rice.
I'm so ready.
I've collected a lot of things
I'll do my best, but I want to bring rice
I'm a sauna.
When I go to the sea abroad, when I go to the sea abroad, when I go to the sea abroad,
When I go to the sea abroad,
When I go to the sea overseas,
When I go to overseas sea
When I go to overseas sea, when I go to overseas sea, when I go to overseas sea, when I go to overseas sea
When you go to overseas sea
When you go to overseas sea, why is it so important?
When you go to foreign waters, when you go to foreign waters, when you go to foreign waters, when you go to foreign waters, when you go to foreign waters, when you go to foreign waters, when you go to foreign waters, it's important because you know you've stepped out a little bit.
I'm a sauna.
I'm not a little bit...
I have really bad ingrown toenails.
I've been saying that for a while.
Have I?
I've been saying it for about two years now.
Ingrown toenails?
I have an ingrown toenail that won't go away.I have an ingrown toenail that won't heal.
If I could make one wish come true, it would be
I wish to have my ingrown toenail fixed.
It's so painful, isn't it?
Please fix my ingrown toenails.
I'm into it in the sauna, but I don't get it done at all.
I haven't figured out how to do it properly yet, which is a bit of a problem.
It would be nice if you could.
I'll do my best.
I want to go on a trip with my friends for a few hours...nice...now I want to wear a projector in the bedroom!
I want to get a projector for my bedroom.
I want one.
What, on the wall? On the top?
You can do it up there.
I'd like to try it up there.
Sure, you can, while you're at it.
It looks like this, right?
That's a good idea.
I'll look for it.
Oh!
Wow, there's a lot of stuff out there that might be good. Let's look for it.
There are a lot of things.
I recently went to Spain.
I liked Spain.
I'd go to Okinawa.
Where's Greece? Where?
Where?
Greece.
I want to go to Europe... maybe Spain.
Which country?
Seven?
Wouldn't that be cool, like a color name?
Yeah, that's cool.
Oh, but it's hard.
It's kind of...
Oh, it's hard.
Violet or something like that...
It's cool.
It's too cool.
Oh, so...
Violet.
Me too, Anne.
It's a very well cared for house cat.
A cat?
Oh, yeah.
I'm a human, too.
I wish I could be a woman.
What about family?
Do you spend time with your family? The same family.
I read.
Again and again I read every day.
It seems to me that if you read it over and over again...
Chens.
SpaceflightSpaceflightRead and rememberWhat are you thinking?
Astronaut.
That's deep.
I know.
Maybe it's me, but I'm afraid of the ocean.
Maybe it was a land animal.
A land animal or a human being.
I feel like I was something that spent a lot of time on land.
That's what you do, you know, travel and climb mountains and stuff.
Yeah, that's nice.
I want to be active.
That's nice.
I want to work in the fields.
I want to do sweet potatoes and stuff like that.
I want to work in the dirt.
Q. What do you think about your life? My life.
Wow, that's nice.
I am family.
Q. What is family?
No excuses.
I'll be honest with you.
I'll say, "Okay, I was sleeping, too.
I love asparagus and bacon.
Graduate school.
I want to drive abroad.I want to drive abroad
I want to go abroad by myself.
Yes, you can.
I can go.
No, I like it here.
No, I don't.
I've had a little bit of that.
You're getting confident.
I've got nothing but good things to say.
If I hadn't gotten in, it would've been a lot harder, you know, and I'd wonder what would've happened.
I've met people, I've had experiences, and it's all good.
The mountains, the ocean, it's scary, isn't it?
The ocean is scary
The ocean is scary it's only true
Mountains, oceans
Scary
Yes, the sea
Now, I'm going to do some incense or something.
I'll put some bath salts in the bath.
Maybe the park? Killer.
I'll go to the park.
We could play there forever.
That's right.
We'd go to all the parks.
Ew!
We did that.
I was like, after school, you know, just running around the park, eh! We were doing that.
Yes, we did.
I used to do that after school.
I was having a flower fair.
What?
That was fun!
Hanaichi Momme.
It was popular.
I don't know, maybe it was the miso soup.
Oh, I don't remember, it was so embarrassing, it was so hot, that's for sure, but maybe it was the miso soup... it spilled.
It was so embarrassing.
It was hot.
That's for sure.
It doesn't happen often.
When I was a kid I spilled miso soup almost every day.
That's right.
So you spilled some for the first time in a while.
That's cute.
It was embarrassing.
I was just going to the convenience store.
I was a little out of it.
All the junk in my pants was open.
When did you realize that?
When I got home.
After you got home?
Just as I was getting into my pajamas.
I thought it was the tower.
I was so embarrassed.
You're lucky you didn't run into anyone.
I'm glad you knew someone.
That was close.
I'm going to say 7, the number 7... and I'm from Itabashi.
I'm from Itabashi, and I like the name "Itabashi".
That combination...
That combination.
That feeling.
I see...
I don't know...
I don't know.
something
something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something...
I love the feeling of something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something.
That feeling.
Q. What do you like to do?
Do what you love and forget about it.Do what you love and forget about it.
I'm of the school of thought that time will take care of itself.
Sleeping, eating, whatever.
I just spend time.
Q. What are your goals for the future?
I'm going to wait until they come out.
I don't know.
I want to ask you the same thing.
Sometimes I wonder how you get motivated.
You're right.
I don't know how to get motivated at times like that.
But if I force myself to move, I can move unexpectedly. Body?
Yes. For example, when I feel tired of doing the laundry or feel unmotivated, I force myself to get up.
Or turn off the TV one more time.
That's the first step, right? That's right. If you take the first step, you can do it.
I use the emoji piece a lot.
I see... it's like a smirk.
You know, like an early smirk, like a black-and-white smirk.
Oh, it's so small!
I get it, I get it, I get it.
Cuddle up.
Cuddle!
You tend to use that emoji.
How do you get that out?
Maybe if you go this way a lot, you'll get it.
I've got it.
Yes, yes, yes!
I'm so happy!
It's been a while since I've seen you.
It's been a long time.
And we're sisters!
Sisters.
I'm so happy.
You're so much stronger than me.
I'm better than you... and we're sisters!
We're sisters.
Anne's so strong, and I'm like, "Ane.
We have a good balance.
I wonder how it was...
During the drama?
I guess you're right.
But I really liked it.
So...
I was so happy.
I thought she was cute.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Is that my line?
No, but I didn't tell him. I just watched him quietly.
I don't know if it's too much to ask... to say I like her.
Oh, really?
I'm glad.
But he was so solid.
From the first time I met him.
I don't know.
You know...
I've been really busy.
I wondered if you were okay.
I talked to her during the crank-in session.
She's very friendly.
She stands in the same section with me.
She's kind and firm.
I'm very happy.
I'm glad.
Oh, my God.
I'm so glad.
I cook a lot.
And I make clothes for dogs.
I've always wanted to be like that.
It's so homey.
I can do that.
I adore it.
I'm...
No, I really said it earlier.
I mean... you're always just being yourself, Naa-chan.
There's really no front or back.
You've always been there.
I think that's what ordinary people can't do.
I think it's wonderful that no matter how busy you are, you can tell that you love your work.
I think it's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy to hear that.I'm glad you enjoyed it.
It was fun.
We got to know each other so much.
It was a great opportunity.
Yes, it was.
I had a great time, too.
I had a great time talking with Nana.
It was a great time.